http://www.westernrangewines.com.au/privacy

HomeOnline ShopSpecialsWinesLimited ReleaseJulimarLot 88Old WellAboutThe WineryCellar DoorThe VineyardsChittering ValleyPhilosophyAwardsExportsVIP ClubEventsContactLocation MapFAQs
Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Western Range Wines may ask users to provide information that personally identifies an individual in certain circumstances, including for example when submitting an enquiry form or order. We use personal information for two primary purposes:
To enable quick and convenient contact with specific individuals who require follow-up services from us.
To create a record of personal information that can be utilised in the future within our marketing and customer service departments, should the need for contact again be necessary.
All requests for removal from such future contact are always honoured.
By not providing the personal information as requested, users will still be able to have access to the Western Range Wines website, but we will not be able to process certain requests that require further communication, such as orders, enquiries and such like.
Western Range Wines never provides any user's personal information to any third-party for commercial or other purposes unless required to do so by law. This is a strict policy that is strictly enforced.
Terms of Use
The content of this website is for information purposes only. Whilst every effort has been taken to ensure the accuracy of the information in this website, users are strongly urged to confirm important information, such as (but not limited to) prices, service availability or event dates, by email or telephone. Western Range Wines cannot be held responsible for any loss or damage resulting from any information contained in this website. Western Range Wines disclaims all warranties, express or implied, as to the accuracy of the information contained in the materials on this website. Information on this website may be printed for personal use while keeping in mind the terms of use above.
Western Range Wines reserve the right, in every case at its own discretion and for whatever reason, to amend content contained within this website, its corporate documentation and promotional material.
Linked Websites
This website may provide links to a number of external websites; these are provided for your convenience. These websites are not controlled by Western Range Wines and neither Western Range Wines, its directors nor employees assume any responsibility or liability for any material contained within such websites.
Copyright Notice
Western Range Wines holds the copyright to this website. Western Range Wines grants you a limited license to view this website utilising the Internet, for either personal or commercial use. You are not permitted to make copies of this website, reproduce or alter this website for any purpose whatsoever without the express written consent of Western Range Wines.
© 2020 Western Range Wines | Privacy Policy & Terms of Use | Powered by jDynamic
